♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ We're down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked
him on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him into space ♪
- [Mike] Let me go!
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ Croooow ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Just repeat to
yourself it's just show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(doors clanking)
- Okay, okay, welcome to the
Satellite of Love, everyone.
Mike, Tom, Crow, and
Gypsy are the names
and Blackjack is the game.
Blackjack 21,
Blackjack blackjack.
- I'll stick!
- You can't stick until I
deal you a card, you loon.
- Okay, I stick now.
Hey this isn't so hard.
- You can't have 21
with just one card.
- Okay, okay, hit me!
No, no, I stick now, I'll stick!
Oh man, I just can't
handle this anymore.
- Should I spit on
your dice now or not?
- Okay, now me,
me, me, me, me, me.
Hit me, hit me, hit me.
- Don't you wanna
check your cards?
- Just keep 'em
comin' bartender.
I said hit me.
Hit me, hit me, hit me.
- This is ridiculous,
you wanna go check
Lou Rawls in the bar?
- Yeah, sure.
- Hit me, hit me,
hit me, hit me.
Hit me, hit me, hit me.
- We'll be right back.
- Hit me, hit me, hit me.
(techno music)
Hit me, hit me.
Okay, I wanna double down.
(Mike groans)
- Hey Mike, you
want I should call
the pit boss over for
to break his thumbs?
- No, well--
- Hey Mike, someone's calling.
- Oh, it's probably Dr.
Fossbender and TV's Fred.
Come in.
- Ah Mike, not that I
care about impressing you
or anything, but check
out my invention exchange.
Ta da, it's the
atomic-powered hair dryer.
How ya doin' down there, Dr. F?
- Oh, I'm fine, Frank.
I'm just trying to
settle on a look.
- That's great.
Be with you in a minute.
- All right.
- Okay Nelson, see if you
can follow me on this one.
Atomic power:
efficient, dirt cheap,
relatively few meltdowns.
Modern hair dryers:
inefficient, expense to run,
and, okay I admit,
relatively few meltdowns.
But my atomic-powered hair dryer
works in a fraction of the time.
- Frank, what look do
you think is better?
The Niels Bohr or
the Richard Feynman?
- Oh, I'd go with the Bohr.
- Really?
- The Feynman would make
your face look too chubby.
- Okay, I'll take
your recommendation.
- Okay, great.
Just gonna put these
goggles on here.
How ya doin', you comfortable?
- Oh, I'm fine.
Frank, is this safe?
- Of course it's safe.
What could possibly go wrong?
You comfortable in there?
- Yes, get on with it! (sighs)
- Okay, hold please.
We have zero quock.
(thunder crashing)
Okay!
Let's see how you're doing.
Get you all combed out here.
See how you look.
I'm sure everything'll
be (screams)
Demon, demon!
Stay away from me! (screams)
- Frank, what is it?
- Oh nothing, nothing,
nothing at all.
Just thought you were
Batwoman there for a minute.
Hair looks great, though, great!
- Oh, thank you.
- Back up to you, Mack.
- I don't get them.
- Um, Mike, our invention?
- Right, Crow take point.
- Okay, let's talk
about unsightly hair
that grows on your
back, back hair.
It's disgusting.
You'll never know
the touch of a woman
unless you rid yourself
of it immediately.
Yuck, bleck!
- Crow.
- Oh, oh, not that
back hair is bad.
Some people might like it.
- Yeah, if you're
alien or something.
- Whatever the case,
our invention is called
the Razor Back, and it
gives you the option
of getting rid of your
back hair if you want to.
- And you should,
for God's sake.
- Now I'll demonstrate on the
back of my jumpsuit because
(chuckles)
I don't have any back hair.
- Yeah, no back hair.
Man's a timber wolf.
- You slather on
the lather with this
specially-made
applicator like that.
- Mm, I love this part.
- And then one stroke
of the feather-like
razor back and all your
back hair problems are gone.
- It's about time,
you big, ugly yax.
- Servo!
- Yeah, but it looks
good on some people!
- What do you think, sirs?
(buzzing)
- Hey, it really is a new you.
- Really?
Geez, I can't believe
you don't have
a mirror around here, Frank.
I'm dying.
(Frank screams)
Anyway Mike, your
movie is called
"The Wild, Wild
World of Batwoman,"
and for all I know it
stars Robert Conrad
and Ross Martin, but I doubt it.
There's also a
short on cheating.
Come on, Frank, I've
gotta see how it came out!
- Don't come near me!
Hair looks great, love it.
- Oh good, good.
- Geez, I really
roughed myself up there.
- I'll say, it's "Sweeney
Todd" playing on your back.
- I got the stick!
- Ah, oh!
(alarm buzzing)
- Stop crying.
- [All] Movie sign!
(doors clanking)
(space ambient music)
- [Mike] Okay, let's go.
(patriotic music)
- [Tom] Cheating, how to make it
work for you at
home and on the job.
(chuckles)
A Centrol Production,
although we got the idea
from a different company,
'cause we're cheating.
Thank you.
A Jack Benny program.
(imitating crowd cheering)
(bell gonging)
- [Mike] Ebenezer Scrooge.
(clock ticking)
- [John] Well, why
don't they call?
- Because they don't like you.
- [John] They've had
plenty of time to decide.
- [Tom] A young Franz
Kafka awaits his fate.
(clock ticking)
- I think I'll go
write some Nocturnes.
(clock ticks)
(phone buzzes)
For depressing phone
sex, dial 1-900-ALFALFA.
- [Tom] (chuckles) The
Foley guy must be calling.
- Hello?
Yes, this is John.
- [Mike] I saw what you did.
- Yes, I know why
you're calling,
They did?
Oh, they did.
- They found the body, huh?
- No, I guess that's it then.
Thanks anyway.
- [Mike] And his parents
officially cut ties.
- [Tom] Good thing
I have my Paxil.
- Geez, this kid could
freak out Jame Gumb.
- [Mike] You know
what this room needs?
A plant.
(imitating party)
- [Tom] Hey come on in, kid!
(imitating gunshot)
(phone rings)
- [Man On Phone] Did you
hear about John Taylor?
They voted him out as Student
Council representative
because he was caught cheating.
- [Mike] Who, John Taylor?
T What's the story
morning glory?
What's the word coming back?
(all chattering)
- [Narrator] You, a cheat, John?
John, what have you done?
- Mother Teresa
called, she hates you.
- [Narrator] Remember
how it all started.
The day you went
over to Mary's house
to study the test.
Remember?
- [Mike] There are
not enough bell towers
in the world for Johnny.
- All right John, now look.
The problem is to factor
x-squared minus 9x plus 20.
Now how do you do it
- Let's just cheat.
- Hm, let's see.
X-squared minus 9x plus 20.
You take the x-squared
minus the 9x and--
- [Tom] Uh-uh, nobody home, huh?
- Oh, you subtract x from
x-squared and then you--
- [Tom] John, this is geography.
- Ah, golly Mary, I
don't anything about
this factoring business.
- John, you do too.
Now the answer is the
quantity x minus five
times the quantity x minus four.
- [Mike] Of course!
- Now do you see how I got it?
- Yeah, I guess I do.
But golly, Mary,
this stuff's awful.
I just don't get most of it.
- You'll just have
to or you won't
pass the test tomorrow.
- I know it.
Mary--
- Will you kill me?
- If I get stuck on the test,
you'll help me, won't you?
- How can I help you?
- It's easy.
Miss Granby hardly ever
comes back to where we sit.
If I get stuck, I'll just
ask you for the answer.
- [Tom] What point!
- Well, I don't know.
- Oh forget it, I probably
won't have any trouble anyway.
- [Narrator] But you
remember what happened
the next day, John.
- [Tom] You committed
a mortal sign.
- [Narrator] Miss
Granby's test was even
tougher than you
thought it would be.
There were a lot of
problems you couldn't work.
And it seemed to
you that you didn't
stand a chance without--
- [Mike] Stop it, stop
the voice in my head!
- [Narrator] And right
there in front of you
sat your pal, Mary,
which her head chock full
of all the answers you needed.
- [Tom] Split it open now.
- [Narrator] You
thought about it.
There you were, desperate.
And there was your salvation,
within arm's reach.
- [Tom] On a doily.
- [Narrator] So you
decided to take a chance.
- Psst, hey Mary,
what's the answer?
- [Narrator] You
asked Mary for help,
and of course Mary, being
Mary, gave you the help.
- Sweet Mary, no, don't!
- [Narrator] It
was all so simple,
you began to wonder why
you'd spent so much time
worrying about the test.
Yes sir, you felt pretty
pleased with yourself.
- [Tom] Yeah!
- [Narrator] You'd put
one over on Miss Granby.
A few days later,
Miss Granby returned
the graded papers.
- [Mike] Your one mistake,
you signed your
test Mary Mathews.
- Oops.
- [Tom] This contract
arrived for you from
a Mr. Ellzebub.
- [Mike] For the first time,
Johnny feels real power.
- [Narrator] Was there
a shadow of doubt
in Miss Granby's face
as she looked at you?
- Or was it lust?
- [Narrator] What was there
for Miss Granby to doubt?
After all, wasn't
this the best grade
you'd ever made on
an Algebra test?
Maybe that was it.
Maybe the grade was too good.
Somehow that odd
little look Miss Granby
gave you seemed to haunt you.
- Did you really earn that 92?
- Oh, hi Miss Granby.
(screaming)
Ah get away!
- [John] Aw, she
didn't mean anything.
That test wasn't very
important anyway.
- Yeah, just keep
telling yourself that.
- [Narrator] You thought
it was just a little thing.
But it was the beginning
of all your troubles.
- [Tom] You talking to me?
Hey!
- [Narrator] After that,
life went on for you
pretty much as usual.
You were busier than
ever with sports.
- [Tom] Shaving points.
- [Narrator] With Mary
and your friend Jim.
And most of all,
with your new job
as Student Council
representative.
- I envision a cheating wing.
- [Narrator] You'd
always wanted to be
on the Student
Council, and you were
really proud of yourself the day
you were elected to
take Jack Martin's place
when he moved out of town.
- [Mike] Under
mysterious circumstances.
- [Narrator] But now,
with the honor of the job,
went the necessity of
keeping your grades up.
- [Tom] And your enemies down!
- [Narrator] And that
was your problem.
- Dear, Joe McGinnis.
I admire, uh oh.
(phone buzzing)
- [Mike] Maybe he'd do
better if he had parents.
- Hello?
- [Jim] This is Jim.
- In the next room.
- [Jim] Let's go down to Sam's
and get a hamburger.
- I can't, Jim, I've
got homework to do.
- [Jim] Ah, don't worry about.
You've got plenty of time.
- [Tom] I will bring
you down, Johnny!
- Okay, let's go
get a hamburger.
I'll see you in a minute.
- Now is this Ingmar Bergman's
first American film?
- [Mike] (chuckles) I think.
(clock ticking)
- [Narrator] The big
clock in the hall
went on ticking off it's
even measure of time.
And you went on as before.
- [Mike] Eating hamburgers
while the world--
- [Narrator] You
and Mary were still
the best of friends,
but Mary had assumed
greater importance to you.
You came to depend
upon her more and more
in your shool work, although
you scarcely realized it.
- [Tom] You worked her
like a punch press, Johnny.
- [Narrator] It
wasn't that Mary was
any smarter than you were.
It was just, well,
that she seemed to
find more time to study.
- [Mike] Well--
- [Narrator] And you were
Student Council representative
and a very busy fellow.
- You gotta help me.
What's the answer
to number nine?
(sighing)
- [Tom] I smell
a big Commie rat.
- [Miss Granby] John,
bring it up here, please.
(imitating alarm)
- Ding ding ding.
- [Tom] Put your pencil down
and step away from your desk!
Fortunately, you're mob ties
will get you off, Johnny.
- Look at that.
Wow, that's randy!
- I'm afraid I'll
have to give you both
zero on the test.
- Jawohl, Mein Fuhrer.
- And both of you
are to report to me
after school, please.
- And so Dana
Plato's career began.
- [Narrator] So you
were caught, John.
You were exposed in
front of the class.
And what's more, Mary
was involved too.
Mary, who was only
trying to help.
- [Tom] Mary, who will
have to take the fall now.
- [Narrator] And
then what happened?
- Spare some change?
- [Narrator] Your classmates
seemed to treat you
a little coldly.
Perhaps it was because
they had studied
and worked hard
for their grades.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Narrator] Maybe they
felt that your cheating
gave you an unfair advantage.
- I belong in hell.
- [Narrator] And their
thoughts about you
were reflected in another way.
- [John] Hey, what's up?
- [Boy] Meeting of
the Student Council.
- They're hanging you in effigy.
- [John] That's funny,
my name isn't on there.
I'm on the Student Council.
- I don't think you'd
wanna come to this meeting.
It's about you.
- Me?
- That's what I hear.
- By the way, have
you seen my rib cage?
- Say, would you mind calling me
after the meeting's
over and let me know
how it comes out.
- No, I wouldn't mind.
- [Mike] We really should be
talking through our lawyers.
- No, I don't say that
what John did was right.
But I do think we ought to
give him another chance.
- You mean you think
we ought to let him
go on being in the
Student Council?
- I think we should.
- Will the Senator yield?
- I don't.
- The council needs a
good representative.
- That's right,
but I don't think
anyone that cheats
should hold an office.
- [Woman] That's right,
I think we should elect
a new representative.
(all talking at once)
- All right, wait a
minute, wait a minute.
We won't get anywhere
by all talking at once.
Are we ready to take a vote now?
- [Tom] Oh, Margaret
Chase Smith.
- All in favor of giving
John another chance,
hold up your hands.
- Whoa.
- All who think we
should elect a new
student council representative,
hold up your hands.
- Oh holy cow.
- Well, I guess most of us
feel the same way about it.
Who's going to tell John?
- I'll tell him.
I said I'd call him when
the meeting was over.
I'll call him as
soon as I get home.
- [Mike] If you want I can
turn him into furniture.
- John?
I guess you know
why I'm calling.
We had that meeting about
you a little while ago.
They decided to elect a new
student council representative.
- [Tom] You've made some
powerful enemies, son.
- I'm sorry, Johnny, but
I guess you know why.
- That you, student councilor?
- [Narrator] Yes,
John knew why it was.
He'd been caught in a
trap of his own making,
and had involved
his friends too.
He know found himself
looked down on
by friends and classmates.
- - [Mike] have to bathe mother.
- [Narrator] But didn't
John really intend
to be dishonest?
- [Tom] Or is he just pure evil?
- [Narrator] Should Mary
share any of the blame?
- Sure.
- [Narrator] Was it
fair of Johnny to
use Mary as he did?
- [Mike] Yeah, she was there.
- [Narrator] And what
about his classmates?
Did John's cheating
hurt them in any way.
- [All] Give us
Barabbas, Barabbas!
- [Narrator] What do you think?
- Riddle me this, Batman!
(laughing)
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] The end
for Johnny at least.
You poor dope.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- [Tom] Oh.
- Hey I have my
four-year TV medallion.
- [Tom] What do you do
when you're branded?
We watch TV.
- Hey maybe it's "Rope."
- Here's your wrist radio.
Wear it at all times.
- Okay, where?
- [Tom] On your wrist?
- If you wanna talk,
push the button.
- Button?
- Not yet.
In a few minutes, you'll
be in direct communication
with the Batwoman herself.
- [Mike] Angels,
you're going undercover
with Adam West.
- [Woman] Are you ready?
- Yeah, sure.
- [Tom] Tonight on the
"Red Shoe Diaries."
- Proceed.
- Yep, still there.
- Under Article
21, paragraph two,
we accept your
allegiance as a Batgirl.
You will obey all rules,
and obey all order
handed through channels.
- [Mike] Weird.
- Now drink this.
- [Tom] It's Alva 66.
- Do I have to?
- [Tom] It's got chunks!
- [Woman] Part of the ritual.
- It's like a party in my mouth,
and everyone's invited.
- Hey, it's good.
(laughing)
- [Tom] Linda cracked
a funny and it's fun.
- Now that you're one
of us, I can tell.
We're vampires, all right,
but only in a synthetic sense.
Drinking the real stuff
went out with Count Dracula.
- So what's this?
- A real groove.
- Honey mint cherry
and strawberry yogurt.
- Wow!
(laughing)
- [Tom] It's like we're
smart, but we're not.
(dramatic music)
- This is one weird sorority!
- [Tom] Wow.
Vampirism, it does a body good.
- [Spectator] Whoa, huh?
- [Mike] Their
five year mission,
to be hot, hot, hot, wow.
- Hey, I gotta do something.
- [Tom] Where, what Mike?
- [Mike] I'll be back,
don't worry about it.
- [Tom] How rude!
- You should have done that
before we got here, Mike.
Where's he going?
- [Tom] He can't do that.
- I know.
- [Tom] Mike, honey,
you're missing it.
We're not gonna tell
you what you're missing.
It's really good!
- [Mike] Coming!
- [Tom] Come on!
- [Mike] Okay, what did I miss?
Sorry.
- Ow, hey.
- [Mike] Excuse
me, coming through.
- [Tom] What did you miss?
- Only the best credits ever.
- [Tom] Um, what
do ya got there?
- [Mike] Huh, where?
- [Tom] What do ya
got in the bowl?
- [Mike] Popcorn.
- You can't have
popcorn in the theater.
- [Tom] What?
- [Mike] Why not?
- Well, you just can't.
What a question, geez.
- [Mike] Well I'm having some.
- [Tom] Geez, you're really some
kind of maverick, aren't you?
- Can I have some?
- [Tom] Yeah, me too?
- Is there butter?
- [Mike] Um, I think it's
just butter-colored topping.
Here.
- Oh.
- [Tom] Let me have some too.
- [Mike] All right, want some?
- [Tom] Yeah, yeah.
- [Mike] Ram it in there.
(crunching)
(laughing)
- I got a hull.
(hacks)
- [Mike] Here, let me get that.
(grunts)
There it is.
- What's your
fingers taste like?
- [Mike] Um, it's that caramel
where, cotton oil I think.
- [Tom] I hate that smell.
- His finger?
- [Tom] No, no, no,
the oil, the topping,
the 30 weights.
- [Mike] Can I ask a question?
Do we have to be paying
attention to the movie?
- [Tom] Oh, Jerry
Warren, well there's
something clever I could say.
- We now join our
confusing sequence
already in progress.
- [Tom] I'm as mad as hell!
- It's a double-wide
phone booth.
Thanks, Trevor.
- [Tom] Little Johnny,
30 years later.
"The Exorcist."
(whistling)
- [Man] Hey mate, have a light?
- Sure, buddy.
- [Mike] Why, sure.
Having trouble getting to
it because of all the money.
God, I got thousands in there.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
(gasps)
- I am trying to give this
gentleman a light, please.
- Just hand over your wallet,
and you won't get hurt.
- Uh, could I take
the money out first?
- All right, fellas.
You want it?
You just have to
come and get it.
- [Mike] The Badfinger murders.
- [Tom] What?
(gun firing)
- [Tom] Okay, you can have it.
- Hey, it works.
(chuckling)
Oh.
- [Mike] As a rule of
thumb, it's not a good idea
to look down the
barrel of a gun.
- [Tom] Or to drop it.
- Oh, well, look at the time.
I got to go.
I have a doctor's appointment.
- [Mike] Well, as long
as I'm down here, I'm
going to take his underpants.
(gasps)
- [Tom] Attention
Michele Pfeiffer.
- Bat Girl 14 to Batwoman.
14 to Batwoman.
Witnessed a hold-up
that turned to murder.
- Didn't do anything about it.
Over.
- I have descriptions.
- Hey, someone's throwing
out good fencing.
- The south alley
behind the Star Club.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
(singing along to music)
- [Tom] Woah.
- [Mike] Holy cow.
That's 40 pounds of butt in
30-pound butt capacity pants.
- Whoo.
(chuckles)
Hey, turn down the high beams.
Wow.
The Batusi and the Twist Rumba.
- [Mike] Patty Duke.
(gasps)
- [Tom] Geraldine.
Oh.
Kinda looks like Yogi Berra.
Sorry.
- Oh, I slipped a disk.
Ohh.
- [Tom] We're in the middle
of a KD Lang fantasy.
Wow.
- Women can just
dance with each other.
It's no big deal.
- [Mike] No.
- [Tom] Think she rats much?
Wow.
- [Mike] No, thank you.
I don't want to play
the crying game.
- Hi, honey.
Can I buy you a drink?
- Okay, a Coke.
- [Tom] Doy.
You have to go over
here to get it,
because it's here, you see.
- How about you, sugar?
- [Mike] Goodbye, pork pie hat.
- Hi, I'm Johnny Two-Time,
uh, Johnny Two-Time.
Heh.
- [Mike] His shirt just
screams British
advertising executive.
(laughs)
- [Tom] Uh, you are
a girl, aren't ya?
I made a mistake one time.
- I'm gonna order a shake.
- [Tom] Yes, yes.
But what does it mean?
- Focus.
(singing along to music)
- [Tom] Um, folks,
take our word for it.
Something happened here.
- Yeah.
Oh, and look.
Andy Capp needs more cigarettes.
- [Tom] Oh, I need
a pack of Rothmans.
- [Mike] And despite
all this, life goes on.
- [Tom] Yee hoo.
- Isn't it great?
(chuckles)
Ha ha.
- [Tom] I'm thinking Yogi Berra.
- Yeah.
Oh, they just put a bunch
of movies in a blender
and pressed the mix button.
- [Tom] That's a
great bar, Freddie.
You were right.
- Oh.
What am I doing in a fake
car on a sound stage?
- You got a good constitution.
Snapped out of it real fast.
- Who are you?
- Never mind.
Just sit still and
behave yourself.
- Where are you taking me?
- On a boat ride.
- You don't have to worry.
You won't get seasick.
We make the cruise all the time.
- My boss.
- This is the first time
that a Bat Girl's gone along.
- [Mike] So you're
opening, Jeff's middling,
and I'm the headliner.
- What do you mean Bat Girl?
- You don't have
to play it dumb.
We know you're one of the
dolls working for Batwoman.
(chuckles)
Why do you think we
put the snatch on ya?
(whistles)
- Recording.
- Where did you say
you were taking me?
- What I said was
for you to sit still.
You do that, you'll make
it easy on yourself.
- [Tom] Hmm, well, forget her.
- I don't like her either.
- Sounds like she's kidnapped.
But her radio's on.
- Call Batwoman.
Central line.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- [Mike] There's a
peeping Zorro outside.
(telephone ringing)
- [Tom] Oh, never fails.
Every time I'm stalking.
Hmm?
Woah.
- Good morning,
College Republicans.
- Batwoman speaking.
Who is this?
- [Mike] Wow.
It's casual day at control bat.
- Picking it up on 05 too.
(sighs)
- Good thinking.
- Should we get outta here?
- All girls in your proximity.
Hang up now and stand
by for instructions.
(doors clanking)
- You know, you guys as
enthralling as this Batwoman
movie is, I just can't get that
cheating short out of my mind.
- Hmm, ditto, friend.
- It posed so many
dilemmas, like did
Johnny intend to be dishonest?
Or should Mary share the blame?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, was Mary just a pawn
in Johnny's little game?
- Which begs the
question of free will.
What about free will?
- Good one.
- And should his classmates
give him a second chance?
- Yeah.
- And why doesn't the accused
get a chance to defend himself?
- Yeah.
- Good point.
And should, uh, Miss
Grandy have just
come into Johnny's bedroom
uninvited and bodiless?
- Oh, that's true.
- What do you think
about that, Crow?
- Uh, uh, the Beatles.
- Oh!
You haven't been
paying attention
at all, have you, Crow?
- Yes.
Uh, could we talk
about Mitchell?
- Now see what I mean?
- Hey, I know what let's do.
Let's answer the
questions that the short
posed in our own
personal essays.
- Oh, sure.
- That's an excellent
idea, Mr. Nelson.
That in and of itself
is a valuable exercise
in articulating one's thoughts
in a clear, concise manner.
- Now what's in it for us.
And by us, I mean me.
- I figured.
- Well, there is those Hostess
Sno Balls I've been saving.
- Oh!
- I also want to be boss
of the ship for a month.
- Oh, we'll talk about that.
- And Servo has to do
my laundry for a year.
Even my underpants.
- You don't even
wear underpants.
- Oh, you don't
worry about that.
I'll take care of that.
- This is getting weird.
We'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Oh.
(tires screeching)
- But you said we'd
be taking a boat.
From the docks?
Or where?
- Look, what I said was--
- Look, you're kidnapped.
Could you act scared?
- Would you give
me that, please.
- [Tom] Hmm?
- So that's your
gimmick, a wrist radio.
Hey, that's not bad.
Not bad at all.
Hey, I'll--
- Hey, batter, batter.
Hey.
- Talking right now.
Testing.
One, two, three.
- [Mike] It works.
- Can you hear me, Batwoman?
(laughing)
(chuckles)
- [Tom] What the hell
is that all about?
- This is Batwoman speaking
to you, whoever you are.
I've a simple warning
that you've taken on
much more than you'll
be able to handle.
- [Mike] There's a Mexican
wrestler lurking outside.
- Transmission to
all girls, 0077.
We're going to hold a
special meeting of code 331
according to
articles in Manual A.
Attendance by entire
membership highly essential.
Don't be late, any of you.
Batwoman over and out.
- Batwoman has a
nice split-level in a
decent neighborhood.
- [Tom] Oh, it's lovely.
Oh, "Beakman's World."
- [Mike] The Aveda Corporation.
(buzzer ringing)
- [Tom] Pons and
Fleischmann, still at it.
(chuckles)
(grunting)
- I really have to go.
Oh, ho, I really mean it.
Oh, hoo Oh, my
teeth are floating.
- [Mike] We have company.
- [Tom] Hey, I will
pet her and keep her
can call her George.
- [Mike] Oh, don't
worry about him.
No social skills, sorry.
- [Tom] Oh, Donald.
- [Man] Nobody's
going to hurt you.
- [Tom] It's Mr. Bill,
and he's all grown up.
- She's a wildcat.
I'd like to belt her one.
- Come on, Bruno.
Lay off her.
(all groaning)
- [Man] A real cutie-pie.
- I'm from next door.
Uh, can I borrow a
beaker or something?
- I must apologize.
- Excuse me, can I, I,
I just need a, a, can I?
I just want to see
what time, can I--
Well, you're busy.
I'll, I'll come back later.
- This just happens
to be one of them.
But you have my promise that
I will make your stay here
just as comfortable as possible.
Oh, back, back,
back, Heathcliff.
- He's my concierge.
He wants to take your bags.
- Heathcliff?
- He's just curious.
- [Mike] Look, he's
packing his brain back in.
- Perhaps you're, uh, somewhat
of a bit curious yourself.
(chuckles)
What about this place?
- I think it's only reasonable
that a little doll is given
our best courtesy, uh,
with a proper introduction.
- My friend, Nicely Nicely.
- I'm known as Tiger.
- [Tom] I'm great.
- I'd, I'd like
you to meet Bruno.
- [Mike] Oh, we met
at the kidnapping.
- This here's Professor Neon.
He's a scientist.
- Great scientist.
- Yeah, yeah.
Neon, he's a great scientist.
- I have perfected, uh,
some of the greatest
scientific discoveries
of the 20th century.
- And I spent a year at Harvard.
- I have no doubt that the
name of G. Octavius Neon
will go down in history as
one of the absolute giants
of civilized science.
- [Tom] Um, yes,
blue-skying here.
- Monstrous, do you?
No, back, back,
back, Heathcliff.
Back, I say.
Now.
(cyberphone beeping)
Well, we've got to go now.
- What do you people
at home think?
- Yes, Rat Fink.
- Rat Fink?
- I see you were able to get
the girl without consequences
or undue complications.
- Yes, Rat Fink.
- Very good.
Your work has been commendable.
You'll be rewarded
in the future.
Now listen carefully.
(blabbering)
I want you to bring me
the girl's wrist radio.
Bring her to my laboratory
within the next hour.
I intend to communicate
directly with Batwoman
on her own frequency.
(gasps)
- [Mike] No.
- I'll have a pipeline into
ever conversation she carries.
It'll be a pleasure
to pay her back
for all the times she's
foiled me in the past.
- Sir, are you sure you
have the right office?
- Your instructions, Neon?
Carry them out.
- Yes, Rat Fink.
- [Tom] Please, it's Rat.
I insist.
- [Mike] Well, something
profound should be said.
But what?
- Meanwhile, in a
completely different movie--
- [Tom] I'll say.
Yeah.
(sighing)
- Wrestling.
- All right, girls.
Business concluded.
The meeting will
come to order now.
Let's hurry up.
- [Tom] We're going to
tabulate the number of cookies
each of you sold.
Excuse me.
- Yes, this is where I stand.
- [Tom] Stop looking
at my butt, Debbie.
- You may take
your positions, 14.
Thank you, Batwoman.
- One, two three.
- [Bat Girls] We, the
girls who are dedicated
to Batwoman, take our
oath with all sincerity.
- [Tom] Uh-huh.
- [Bat Girls] We, the
girls who are dedicated
to Batwoman, take our
pride with all sincerity.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- [Bat Girls] We, the
girls who are dedicated
to Batwoman, fight against
evil with all sincerity.
- [All] One nation, under Hef.
- Let's hurry up.
- [Tom] Next time, can we
just say the serenity prayer?
(imitating squeaking)
- [Tom] After you, Tawny.
Cute suit, Sherrie.
- [Mike] Don't sit on the couch
with your wet suits, girls.
- Tina, I want to sit
by Batwoman this time.
- [Tom] Now the girls in
acquisition have a plan.
- In view of the fact that
this is a special meeting--
- [Tom] And incredibly goofy.
- The time element
must work in our favor.
- [Tom] Tony Field has a tattoo.
- I think it's advisable
that we dispense
with roll call and all
formalities under Pact 440-616.
- Second the motion.
All in favor?
- [Bat Girls] Aye.
- Motion carried, Batwoman.
Continue with business.
- Thank you
- Robert's Rules of Wow.
- [Mike] Holy cow.
- That I feel intuitively
that the rescue plan we work
out will ultimately succeed.
But at the same time will offer
hazardous conditions
for you all.
I feel strongly that if--
(radio clicking)
- [Tom] Sorry, I pooted.
- [Woman] She got
her radio back.
- [Rat Fink] No,
my young friend.
I'm happy to inform you the
girl did not get back her radio.
She won't until I'm
ready to return it.
Are you surprised, Batwoman?
Do you know whose voice
you're listening to?
- Dennis James?
- I'm afraid I do.
And the surprise is
not a pleasant one.
Well, I might have known
you were behind this.
What have you done
with that girl?
- [Tom] I've introduced
her to Phil Donahue.
- [Rat Fink] Except to extend
some very comfortable
accommodations.
She'll be returned to you
quite safely, Batwoman.
- [Tom] Or you can
take the curtain.
- What is the price
you're asking?
- [Rat Fink] You know
me better than that.
- [Tom] Mr. Fink, turn
your radio down, please.
- [Rat Fink] Simply
need your help
to enter a certain building
and secure a certain item.
- I'll give you certain
specifics at a certain time.
- [Rat Fink] Off in your line.
I'm sure that you can
understand that the operation is
a delicate one.
If I had some skillful enough
to carry it out for me,
I wouldn't have put
myself to all this bother.
- [Mike] That Fink's
got a good watch voice.
- [Rat Fink] It is not
necessary to discuss
the consequences
if you refuse to oblige me.
- Obliging you is bitter
enough consequence in itself.
- Ouch.
- But I'll not take
the risk of that girl
losing her freedom
because of me.
You win, Rat Fink.
But I insist upon
seeing her first.
- [Rat Fink] Your distrust of me
is grossly
unjustified, Batwoman.
However, I'll agree
to your terms.
12 o'clock on the top
of Hangman's Bluff.
- [Tom] Near Dead Man's Curve.
- [Rat Fink] My men
will meet you there.
- [Mike] You think they
get telemarketing calls
on those wristwatches?
Well, it looks like Rat Fink's
doing all right for himself.
(sobbing)
- [Tom] Woah.
- Give her another
happy pill, will ya?
Can't stand it.
- [Mike] She's had
a breakthrough.
- [Tom] Here, have a Mentos.
Fresh goes better.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
Dreezle drazzle drazzle drome.
Time for this one to go home.
- Just one of my many
spectacular feats.
I could make you so happy, you
wouldn't believe it possible.
- Here.
Why don't we all sit down and
make ourselves comfortable?
I got some chocolate
milk in the refrigerator
and some macaroons.
Go ahead, sit down.
- Well, I don't normally
do this at meetings, but...
- [Tom] Just park
your bucket, Cher.
She's got a frontal bike rack.
Woah.
(growls)
- [Mike] Criminy.
It's like a Warhol movie,
except it's kind of weird.
- [Tom] Chaka Khan would be
ashamed to dress like her.
- Uh, none for me, thanks.
I'm lactose intolerant.
- How long am I to
be kept waiting?
- Oh, not for long, I'm sure.
- [Tom] Hey.
- At any moment, I expect that--
(cyberphone beeping)
(laughs)
There you are.
You see, no sooner
said than done.
Oh, you can call--
- [Mike] Kind of an
odd Thanksgiving,
but the sentiment's there.
- [Tom] Oh, yeah.
(upbeat music)
(chuckles)
(cyberphone beeping)
- [Tom] I turned
the switch on, boss.
- Well, my adversary.
So we meet again.
- [Mike] Him again.
- [Rat Fink] Welcome to
my humble facilities.
- So we meet again.
But for the first
time on your terms.
- [Mike] Have some Rolaids.
Calcium.
- I can't recall ever being
placed in a position where
I would perpetuate
your evil plans.
- Now you might think
that the iocane powder is
in this one.
- There are great things
we can do together,
things that could bring
unheard of power and riches
to both of us.
- [Tom] Is she doing a
rain dance back there?
- I'm only here
because I have to be,
and it won't be for
much longer at that.
Get on with your dirty business.
- [Mike] She brings a
quiet dignity to this film.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- As I've mentioned
previously, I want
you to get something
for me that I
wanted personally
for a long time.
- Mittens.
- [Rat Fink] The
Ayjax Development
Corporation has developed
an atomic hearing aid--
- [Tom] We'll destroy
Miracle-Ear and rule the world!
- Any telephone
conversation desired.
Since it has this
potential, the government
has refused the patent.
- [Mike] I, I, I, I, I.
(mumbling)
(groaning)
- [Tom] Sieg Heil.
- [Rat Fink] An assignment such
as this would be entirely within
the realm of your own
many splendid talents.
- [Mike] What can you say?
It's a tour de force
comic performance.
- Every--
- [Rat Fink] Neon,
you idiotic fool!
What do you think you're doing?
- [Tom] I got the music in me.
- I must have switched
the, the glasses, Batwoman.
I, I only wanted to show
you how wonderful they are.
I could make you happy.
- Oh, his parents
must be so proud.
(babbling)
- [Mike] Hey,
you're a guest here.
Ouch.
(upbeat rock music)
- [Tom] Where's
that coming from?
- Well, we've discovered
Batwoman's secret power.
She can open unlocked doors.
- [Tom] So this is the wild,
wild world of Batwoman, eh?
Hmm?
- [Mike] What happa?
- [Tom] Ohh.
- [Tom] Yes, it's the best hits
of the '50s and '60s on
8-track and cassettes.
- [All] Tequila.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- Those two were once
cute, tiny, lovable babies.
- [Mike] Tequil, oh.
- [Tom] Meanwhile well in Rome.
- [All] Aye-ja- Aye-jax?
Aye-jax.
Ai-yi-yi,
Aie.
- We're in trouble
- [Tom] Hmm?
- [Mike] I have no idea what
I'm doing in this movie.
- Deep, deep trouble.
- Oh, take it easy, JB.
We don't have to
throw in the sponge
just because we're
hanging on the ropes.
- [Tom] Hmm?
- That's an understatement.
I'd say it was more like
being pulled to the corner
after a nine cone.
(chuckles)
- Oh, Larry Tate, that's rich.
- Now, look, I have the legal
department working overtime.
- [Tom] And she's really tired.
- We've got plenty of time to
come up with something, JB.
- Look, Flanagan--
- [Mike] That's me.
- There's been some
speculation in my mind
about talking to you.
- Oh, really?
- [Mike] That's good.
You weren't in the office.
- I'm afraid there
exists a few aspects
to this business about our
patent being denied that, well,
that I haven't brought
out fully before.
- And you're
sitting on my lunch.
- A few weeks ago I was
contacted by a foreign agent.
- [Tom] This just in.
- A foreign agent?
You didn't make a deal
with them, did you?
- Well, of course I didn't.
- [Mike] I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to lash out.
- Stories carried
by his cronies,
I'm sure a few people
assumed that I did.
Oh, look, Flanagan,
I realize you've
got our legal boys
trying to concoct
some sort of appeal for us.
But the terrible thing is--
- [Tom] You're on
my tuna sandwich.
- I never told you this either.
Our time limit for destroying
that device has run out.
- [Tom] What device?
Who are you?
- We had just 15 days,
not 30 as I told everyone.
- JB, you kept that
thing here illegally.
- [Tom] You dope.
- Hoping we wouldn't
have to destroy it?
- Well, get ready for
the worst part of all.
- [Mike] I've hired
Willie Tyler and Lester.
- I received a telephone call
early this morning
from Batwoman.
- [Tom] Hmm?
- She was good enough to
inform me to be on the alert
that extensive
planning was being
executed for an attempted theft.
- Does she know
that to be a fact?
- If she didn't, she
wouldn't have called.
- [Tom] I have no clue
what you're talking about,
but I'm profoundly devastated.
(gasps)
- Well, now that you've informed
me of our legal position,
I suppose asking
the police for help
is highly questionable, JB.
- [Tom] I oughta--
- Why didn't you tell
me about this sooner?
What do you think I'm here for?
- I want you to spank me.
- I was afraid.
And I was hoping for
some kind of appeal
to the patent office.
- [Mike] And I didn't
steal no bike neither.
- Well, we've just gotta think
of something to tighten it up.
That's all.
- You just don't care about
my lunch at all, do you?
You know it's there, and
you deliberately sit on it.
- Wait a minute.
- We're not supposed
to be in this movie.
- Wait a minute, JB.
I think I've got it.
- [Mike] The rain in Spain
falls mainly on the plains.
- Batwoman.
(gasps)
(chuckles)
- With her, we might
see some light yet.
(upbeat jazz music)
- [Mike] It's over.
(clapping)
(all groaning)
Now this shot here,
this is pure Warren.
- [Tom] Thursday afternoon,
I pulled up at this one place.
I don't know what time it was.
I kind of got out of my car.
I looked at the place.
I walked towards some
sort of structure
in which people
possibly dwelled.
I noticed the agriculture.
The sound editor added
a tasty sax lick.
I passed a tree or a
shrub of some variety.
Then I arrived at the door.
(mysterious orchestral music)
Ooh.
I went through the door,
and it was quite cool.
I had heard Batwoman had
quite a lingerie collection.
I decided to investigate.
(light organ music)
Hmm?
- [Mike] D'oh!
The one day they
aren't wearing bikinis
is the day I stopped by.
(groans)
- Oh, good.
Here's the receptionist.
- [Tom] Are you with
the bride or the groom?
- I'm with you.
Hey, weren't you
in "Beast Master 2,
"Through the Portal of Time"?
- [Tom] Toccata
and wow in D minor.
(purrs)
- You know it.
Oh, she's jamming right now.
She might be a while.
- [Mike] After six months of
lessons from Schmitt Music,
I'm playing for my friends.
- [Tom] Mm, sorry.
This is a smoke-free cult.
You know, for a movie.
(chuckles)
- [Mike] That was Michael
Murry on "Pipedreams."
- I wonder if it's
hard to sight-read
through those glasses.
- [Tom] I bet.
- Batwoman.
- [Mike] Hi.
- Oh, uh, about that door,
that's a little
dangerous, isn't it?
- [Tom] He's really going to
stick to that vinyl, you know.
- It wouldn't have
operated if you
had no appointment or
someone was following you.
You were monitored
electronically
from the time you left your car.
- Oh, really?
- [Tom] Yeah, right.
- Oh, you mean like a
closed circuit television.
- Something like that.
- [Mike] Jell-O shot, ma'am?
- [Tom] Hmm?
- Would you like
some refreshments?
- Uh, no, no, thank you.
I'm fine.
Uh, very nice of you to
see me this way, Batwoman.
And I want you to know
that JB and the rest of us
(glugging)
will be forever grateful
if, well, if you can just
figure out some way to help us.
(all shouting)
- [Mike] I hate those.
- Someone who would listen in
to someone else's conversations.
- Oh, Batwoman, you
really don't think that,
that JB and I would--
- Jim Beam?
(chuckles)
- [Mike] Justice Brothers.
- Oh, I'm not interested in
anyone else's conversation.
No, no.
You have the wrong
idea, entirely wrong.
- [Tom] Is this supposed
to be an all-staff meeting?
- As a matter of fact,
the atomic power structure
was much more revolutionary
than anything we had counted on.
- [Mike] Hey.
You'd think just
being Batwoman she'd
have more exciting meetings,
but this is just painful.
- Goes, it really goes.
But the main thing
is if we could just--
- [Tom] Now what?
- Hang onto it until
our appeal is okayed--
- So there's a subplot
about a horseshoe then.
- [Tom] I guess so.
- A little bit more development,
we can make a great
contribution to, uh, society.
- [Mike] Will you--
- [Tom] Gimme.
- But the big problem
is, Batwoman--
- [Tom] Let me have it.
- If it's stolen, we're sunk.
If our device is
misused, Batwoman,
there's no telling what
can be accomplished.
(grunting)
- [Mike] You have
beautiful eyes.
- Do you realize there
will be no privacy?
And just consider the
danger if they find out
about the cobalt mechanism.
- [Tom] Stop it.
Would you stop it back there?
- I can see it's--
- [Mike] Let's get outta here.
- Avoided at any cost.
- Oh, good, you'll do it.
You'll come in with us.
- Give me some time
to talk with my girls.
I'll call you within the hour.
- Fine, fine.
(upbeat music)
- And in preparing my report
on today's cheating short,
I listened to both
the muse and the sage,
the spirit and the
pragmatist, the mythical
roots of my eternal--
- Oh, any time this
century, Disraeli.
- Crow, come on.
- Oh, okay, Mike, just
wake me when it's over.
- Anyway, as I was saying,
it was the third question
that most intrigued me.
The query, was it fair for
Johnny to use Mary as he did,
is a mental minefield.
I had to be careful, being
the humist that I am.
I left no stone unturned.
- Any time, Servo.
Any time.
- Uh, that answer,
my friends, is no.
Thank you.
- No?
- That's right.
Nyet, nein, negigey.
- That's your report,
the answer is no?
What about all
these other volumes?
- Well, jeez, Mike,
I had several ibids,
30 pages of footnotes,
an extensive bibliography,
and some really neat diagrams
charting the dielectric
process from the Freudian--
- You know, Tom,
you frighten me.
So we're done, huh?
- No, we're not done.
We've still got Gypsy.
Why don't you go
ahead there, girl?
- Yeah.
- Um, oh, oh, okay.
Um, cheating.
By me.
- Hm.
- Cheating is bad.
Richard Baseheart is good.
Well?
- Huh.
Great.
- Well, that was
very good, I thought.
- Yeah, very nice.
- It was spirited, succinct.
Very nice.
- Right to the point.
- Great.
- Can't we just
hand these in, Mike?
I mean, notify me by mail.
- No, no, no, no.
It's your turn.
Now let's hear it.
Come on.
- Oh.
Cheating.
(clears throat)
Cheating is bad.
Richard Baseheart is good.
- Ooh.
- So how about some lunch?
- Hey, Crow.
- What?
- That was word-for-word
the same report
that Gypsy just gave.
(chuckles nervously)
- Wow.
What are the odds
of that happening?
- It's, it's not
exactly the same.
I, I mean the read
was totally different.
Uh, my downbeat was on good.
Uh, Gypsy's was on Richard.
- Scold him, scold him.
Cheater, cheater!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Calm down.
You know, this is
serious business,
and we'll talk about it.
But right now we've got
a movie to get through,
and that's what
we're going to do.
- We, we must demolate him.
Get a match.
Burn him.
(alarm buzzing)
- Ah.
Movie time.
Saved by the bell.
- Burn him!
Burn, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I just lost it.
- Up close.
Come on.
- [Mike] Huh?
(chuckles)
- Right here.
- [Tom] Little
piggy, little piggy.
- [Mike] Heathcliff
shops at Tatters.
- I have something for you.
(chuckles)
Now open your mouth.
- I hope that's cyanide.
- Oh, Heathcliff, this
is not going to hurt you.
- [Mike] It's going to kill you.
- I just perfected
a new formula,
and I must test its reaction.
Whatever it does, it will
only last for a short time.
- [Tom] And it will
pad the film immensely.
- Oh, come on.
Open your mouth.
Oh, Heathcliff, I'm losing
my patience with you.
- Yeah.
I bet he's lost a
lot of patients.
- [Mike] Oh, shut up.
- I'll tell you,
I'll tell you what.
If you take this pill--
- [Tom] I will stop
talking like Gandhi.
- When I go to that underground
cave, I'll take you with me,
and you'll be able
to see some monsters.
You can watch them all the time
that I am in the big cavern.
- Because I'm vaguely European.
- Wouldn't you like that?
Hmm?
Huh?
(Mike sighs)
- [Mike] Ohh.
Trying to be both a
mother and a father to you
is so difficult.
(buzzer ringing)
- [Tom] Could this
please be the end
of the pill-taking scene?
(mock sobbing)
Please.
(cyberphone beeping)
- Welcome back.
Is that the show, then?
- [Tom] Oh.
Heh.
- [Rat Fink] Neon, I
want to let you know
that I'm completely disgusted
with the work of all
of you over there.
- [Mike] I think he
speaks for all of us.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Rat Fink] The
escape of the girl
has all but ruined
my last chance.
We leave now with very little
time to form a new plan.
- I'm sorry about what happened.
- [Tom] Yeah, well, sorry
don't pay the gas bill, doctor.
- Around now.
How is it coming at the cave?
How are all my monsters?
- Never mind about the monsters.
Keep your thinking on
what has to be done.
It's going to be more
difficult than ever
now because I have learned
through the grapevine
that Batwoman herself is
guarding the vault at Ayjax,
taking no chances
of our formulating
a successful operation.
But we'll do it anyway.
Success will be ours.
Do you understand me, Neon?
- Oh, could you
start again, right
after the part where
you were reaming me?
Well, the ball's in
our court, Heathcliff.
(thunder crashing)
- [Mike] It was a
dark and stormy, oh.
- What's Dwight
Eisenhower doing here?
- [Tom] Security
guards of foreign wars.
(humming)
- [Mike] The last brownshirt.
- Where was I on the
night of April 14th?
(chuckles)
I love my job.
- [Tom] Oojay?
Oojay?
Oy, work really piled up
on me while I piled up.
(chuckles)
I love that story.
(telephone ringing shrilly)
(all shouting)
- Oh, jeez.
- [Mike] Phew.
Wow.
- The phone's ringing.
It's never done that before.
All right.
I'm coming.
Keep your chin on.
Hello?
- Hello?
Good evening.
(mumbling)
- [Tom] Hmm?
- No, no one is here.
Everything is in order.
- [Mike] Even your
Markie Mark poster.
- All right.
Bye.
- I'm not going to tell
him what I'm wearing.
He knows already.
- [Tom] It's like "Goldfinger."
- Well, that went
off without a hitch.
- [Tom] Baskin-Robbins, anyone?
(laughing)
- [Mike] This movie's funny.
I changed my mind.
- [Tom] Like he's got a
funny bow tie under his nose,
and it's funny.
(laughs)
- They're doing a classic bit.
This is great.
(laughs)
- [Tom] It's fun when it's fun.
- Yeah, like the White
House Plumbers, only funny.
- [Mike] There's funny
Cheech Marin in the back.
(laughs)
Oh.
Hmm.
- Well, I never would
have believed it.
- I'm Norm Crosby.
- This is wonderful.
(chuckles)
- Thank you.
- [Mike] Hi.
- Ah, my mother had
a pair of those.
(chuckles)
- [Tom] Oh.
- Yes, this is wonderful.
- [Tom] With all this paneling.
- You'll notice I have a
double guard consisting
of my best girls at
the vault itself.
I hope you'll be
able to relax now
that you're aware of the
extent of our precautions.
- Oh, yes, yes.
Of course I will.
Uh, you've made me feel
completely secure, Batwoman.
- [Mike] It's the all
exposition channel.
- I have the only key to the
vault right here in my pocket.
Uh, maybe you could do
with a little bit of lunch?
We can get it right downstairs.
- I think they're
falling in love.
- [Mike] Hey, let's just
be quiet and enjoy this.
It'll go faster.
- [Tom] Yeah.
(sighs)
- Soup?
Hot soup, girls.
- [Tom] Huh?
- Here it is.
Soup.
Get your soup, girls.
Isn't that delicious?
- [Tom] Yes, Bat
Girls come running
for the good taste of hot soup.
- [Man] Atta girl.
How's that taste?
- It tastes like air.
But then everything
tastes like air to me.
(giggles)
(sighs)
- [Mike] Stanley Owsley
is smiling somewhere.
(bat girls giggling)
Dance and guns and
soup don't mix.
- [Tom] Mm-mm.
- Oh, he's reading
"Mr. Drysdale Monthly."
- Uh, Miss Benson?
I'm going to the commissary
for a quick bite of lunch.
Uh, ring through to me if
that Simpson call comes in.
- Simpson, eh?
- Miss Benson, did you hear me?
- [Mike] What's
happened to Miss Benson?
Find out on the next episode.
- Miss Benson?
(upbeat jazz music)
- [Mike] Robert
Guillaume is Miss Benson.
(chuckles)
- And so we leave
on our search for Miss Benson.
(upbeat jazz music)
- [Tom] Gee, pick any
Miss Benson you want.
- Whoo hoo.
♪ Hey, listen to the story
about a man named Jed ♪
♪ A poor ♪
- [Tom] Yee hoo.
- [Mike] D'oh!
Just when I thought the
movie couldn't get any worse.
Ringo's in it.
- [Tom] No.
(upbeat jazz music)
Looking very relaxed,
Hugh Beaumont on sax.
(scatting)
Oh, Justice Ginsberg arrives.
Huh?
- Ah, table five, all women.
Yech.
- [Tom] What the,
(chuckling)
- The Hudson Brothers in
their wackiest comedy yet.
- [Tom] Oh, no.
They're going to
drug Gerry Mulligan.
- Huh?
- [Mike] This is
like a Mentos ad.
(chuckles)
- [Tom] LSD-25 for you.
And you had the LSD-25.
And over here, hot pasta--
- Hey, Hitler!
We want our order over here.
- [Mike] Just a minute.
- [Tom] The LSD-25 for you.
And LSD-25.
- Sandwich.
A sandwich.
Oh.
(chuckles)
Well, I guess this is the, uh--
- [Tom] What?
Huh?
- Uh, this is good
enough for a starter.
- [Man] Oh, go on.
(sighs)
- [Mike] I have feeling Satan
would regret making this movie.
- Look at that.
- Ah, Gloria Steinem gets down.
- [Tom] This was back
when Yiddish theater
was still going strong.
- She's wearing a
gownless evening strap.
- [Tom] Oh, that was
a really good batch.
(laughing)
- You know, these Applebee's
are really getting zany.
- [Mike] Look out.
Here comes the entire waitstaff
singing "Happy Birthday."
- [Tom] No.
(laughs)
(sighs)
- Now this is a
hot lunch program.
(purrs)
Then slurp that down.
Wow.
- [Mike] I've never
seen Solzhenitsyn
look quite so giddy.
- [Tom] Mm-mm.
- He's happy.
All right.
Let's do that Steve and Leo bit.
Here, okay.
- [Tom] Yes, it's a
life in the theater.
- [Mike] First one's
free, Batwoman.
(laughing)
- Give me the keys.
Yeah.
- [Mike] Check out Shirley
Chisholm in the background.
(giggles)
♪ Chisholm, Shirley Chisholm ♪
(laughing)
- He's fun, that one.
(chuckles)
- [Tom] Stevens?
(laughing)
- Have you lost your mind?
- No.
- [Tom] Just my self-respect.
- Now I've lost my mind.
- [Mike] Now this is how the
NRA wants the world to look.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
(chuckles)
- [Mike] And frankly--
- [Tom] Hey.
The Maidenform woman,
you never know where
she'll show up.
- [Mike] Uh, I pick you.
(chuckles)
- [Tom] Hey, Frank Sinatra, Jr.
- Come on.
- Wait.
I'm trying to figure this out.
Oh, where do the batteries go?
- [Man] Tiger, come on.
- [Tom] Okay.
Uh, so you want to go
have soup sometime?
- [Mike] The Landers
Sisters get down.
- I'm Peter Graves.
Tonight on "A&E
Biography," we've
repackaged a documentary
made years ago.
- [Tom] There's a man on
the wing of the plane!
(gasps)
- [Mike] No, there isn't.
- [Tom] Oh, sorry.
- Are you the Beatles?
Oh, you must be the Beatles.
- How's your throat?
- Well, it's actually
feeling quite well.
- It sounds much better.
- [Mike] Geraldine Ferraro.
- What do you know?
Oh, sure.
Go ahead and use the phone.
(clears throat)
- [Tom] Hi, mom.
Practice is done.
Can you pick us up?
- Is this Ayjax
Development Corporation?
- [Mike] Is Perseus
in right now?
- This is Seltzer of
the patent office.
I'd like to speak to
JB Christians, please.
- I'm here with Doodles Weaver.
- He's where?
- [Mike] Up my what?
(chuckles)
- The home of Batwoman?
- [Tom] Should I repeat
everything you say?
- What's happened
that's so terrible.
- [Mike] They've
renewed "Mad About You"?
- Well, yes, I can
get over there.
Well, should I call first?
- Oh, you're right.
I am calling.
- I see.
All right.
We'll take a cab and
get there right away.
- [Tom] We'll take DC Cab.
- What's your address?
Mm-hmm.
- [Mike] Mm hmm.
- [Tom] Hm.
Long address.
- [Mike] Special appearance
by George "Goober" Lindsey.
(chuckles)
Shh.
Mass has already started.
(upbeat jazz music)
- We must concentrate
ourselves fully and, thusly,
penetrate into the realms
of etheric existence.
- Looks like they're
coming down from the soup.
- We must call upon
any spirit guide.
who will contact
those at this table
within the next few moments.
- [Tom] Hmm.
- [Woman] May we hear a voice--
- [Tom] Did we
come at a bad time?
- [Woman] A sign
that this message
is being received
by those beyond
the physical plane.
- [Mike] Judy, Judy, Judy.
- We call out to the
world of spirits.
Will someone please
come through?
- [Man] I am--
- [Tom] Iron Man.
(chuckles)
- [Man] Do you hear me?
- [Mike] He's a contact
of Leonard Cohen.
- Yes, we hear you plainly.
I wish to thank you
for coming to us.
- [Mike] She looks
like a dry fly.
(giggles)
- [Man] It is
perfectly all right.
- I am the north wind.
- [Man] Can I do for you?
- It is desired by
those at this table--
- That we get more bread.
- To locate a missing device,
one of an electronic nature.
It was stolen from
Mr. Christians' here
only a few hours ago.
- [Mike] Oh, yeah.
I got a psychic
bulletin on that.
- Locating it immediately, as
it could be highly dangerous.
- [Mike] And highly dull.
- Individuals who
harbor it may not
be aware of its
explosive potential.
- [Mike] Hmm.
(babbling)
- [Mike] What the--
(laughing)
- I'm afraid I'll have to ask
you to repeat the message.
- [Tom] What was that?
Eek-a-Mouse?
- It sounded like Chinese.
- [Man] I am sorry.
- [Mike] Sir, sit
closer to the mic now.
- [Man] Give more information.
- [Mike] Look at this guy.
Rigor mortis has set in.
- The device was stolen from
the Ayjax Development Company.
I'm aware of the
thief's identity
but not his whereabouts.
He has a hidden laboratory
somewhere along the coast.
- Hey, who doesn't anymore?
- I was there a short
time ago, but it
was in the middle
of the night, and I
was unable to take note
of any landmarkings.
The location of
this laboratory is
what we ask you to help us with.
I must emphasize again
that it's most important.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
(babbling)
(all groan)
- [Mike] Yoko, no.
- You're speaking
in Chinese again.
I have to inform
you that no one here
is familiar with
Oriental languages.
- [Tom] Hey, that's
Asian languages, sister.
- Speak to us only in English.
Do you understand?
- [Mike] Please, god,
cut away to anything.
Please.
- [Man] That speaks
another tongue.
(mimicking babbling)
- [Tom] We know.
(giggling)
- [Man] Another entity.
(babbling)
(all laughing)
- [Tom] Oh, for crying out loud.
- [Man] Now there's no
need to lash out, really.
- The channel free
so I can communicate
with the other gentleman?
- Would you just please leave?
- I feel they're
trying to assist us.
However, I can't comprehend
a word you're saying.
(babbling)
- [Tom] You know, that
may not really be Chinese.
- [Mike] Ah.
- And may we get on
with the information?
- [Tom] Hm.
- Uh, (babbling)
no?
No?
- We have a clear channel now.
You can speak to us.
- I've brought some of
my most important clients
to this seance.
If you could please cooperate.
- It seems we've
lost communication.
- [Mike] Good.
- Uh, look--
- [Tom] Oh, he's alive.
He moved.
Hey.
- Do you think we might
do this some other time?
Oh, don't misunderstand
me, Batwoman.
I do have confidence.
- [Tom] Hm.
- Well, anything you
say, Mr. Christians.
You know your schedule
better than I do.
(sighs)
- [Mike] To every asian
and every human being,
we apologize for that scene.
- Mr. Seltzer.
- Captain Spaulding.
- What is all this nonsense?
And what's happened
to that hearing aid?
Did I hear correctly
about it being stolen?
- Well, uh--
(babbling)
Uh, Mr. Seltzer, I'd like
you to meet Batwoman.
She's our hostess here.
- I am aware of that.
How do you do, Batwoman.
- [Mike] I'm Tubby Guy,
and that's Nerdy Guy
with the briefcase.
(clears throat)
- This is Broglie, my assistant.
He can't speak.
Laryngitis.
(chuckles)
- Like our guest at the table.
(laughs)
- [Tom] Yeah, the ta, oh.
- Well, I could get you
something warm from the bar.
It might loosen up the throat.
- Uh, it would seem
to me that things
are loose enough around
here as they are.
(ominous orchestral music)
- [Mike] Did he rip that
thing out of a Chevy Vega?
(chuckles)
- [Tom] Watson, come here.
I hate you.
- I'm cleaning my oven.
(giggles)
(Tom beatboxing)
- [Tom] Please turn
your head and cough.
Hm?
(groans)
- Oh, god.
This is hit nude.
Damn.
- Haven't you ever tried it?
- Me?
Nah.
Nearest thing I
ever got to exercise
was a couple of strolls every
day when I was up at State.
- You went to State University?
- [Man] University?
- [Mike] The hilarity
of "Drop Dead Fred."
- University?
State pen.
- [Woman] You should
have given college a try.
(babbling)
I went for a year and a half.
- Is that where you
learned to dance?
You're the best
dancer I ever seen.
- [Tom] And I seen two.
- Thanks.
- Gee, I, I'm sorry about that.
- Sure you are.
- I am, really.
- So Mike, this is hell.
- I guess I shouldn't have--
- [Mike] Yep, yep
- On you again.
- [Tom] I guess I should
have put the mic closer too.
- By Rat Fink himself.
He's coming up
here from the cave
to shake my hand personally.
(gasps)
- [Mike] You know Rat Fink?
- [Man] As Neon finishes
that hearing aid.
- Oh, looks like a rather large
and ungainly hearing aid to me.
(chuckles)
(upbeat music)
- Calling all girls in the
north and middle sectors.
- [Mike] That's a lot of girls.
- The beach you're
searching is the least
likely to be the correct one
because that laboratory uses
high voltage, and there
isn't any on the north beach.
- [Tom] Ah,
(babbling)
(giggles)
- But I did see a small reef
in the water just offshore.
Keep your eyes--
- [Mike] Calm down, Batwoman.
- Open for a hidden
cove that would be
completely covered at high tide.
(telephone rings)
Batwoman out.
- [Tom] My other
wrist is ringing.
- Batwoman speaking.
- This is Flanagan, Batwoman.
- [Mike] Hey, the producer.
(laughs)
- I just called to
tell you goodbye
and to thank you
for everything you
did for the Ayjax
Development Company.
- [Tom] I love you, and
I've always loved you.
- Take that.
And also the fact that, well,
I was able to dance with you.
And I want you to know
I really enjoyed it.
- He's a lonely, lonely man.
- Oh, I'm not a
drinking man, Batwoman--
- [Mike] No.
- But, well, I figured
I'd have a couple--
(babbling)
In view of the fact that
I'm leaving immediately,
and I'm starting a new
life in the Fiji Islands.
- [Tom] Cool.
- I'd suggest you pull
yourself together, Flanagan.
There's no need for you
to run off anywhere.
- [Mike] Oh, she does
phone counseling too.
Sweet.
- I can see my work
is cut out for me.
And, and I'll accept it gladly.
- [Mike] Now hold on
while I trace the call.
- All of them, are dedicated
to finding your device.
- [Mike] Excuse me?
- Right now they're
out searching,
working with
selfless dedication.
- [Tom] Oh.
(upbeat rock music)
♪ You keep your
eye on the road ♪
♪ And your hands
up on the wheel ♪
- Oh, Edith Prickley goes
at it with Lumpy Rutherford.
(laughs)
(humming along with music)
♪ Yes, the devil made
this movie for you ♪
♪ Yes, the devil had some time ♪
♪ There's no edit ♪
- [Tom] The sad thing is,
they're trying to tap dance.
(chuckles)
Kill me.
- So do you like me?
(mumbling)
- [Mike] Snap him over.
Break him in half.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- Whoo hoo.
(humming along with music)
- [Tom] Ow.
Oh.
- Barbara Streisand.
- [Tom] Oh.
This is before they
invented Librium, isn't it?
(chuckles)
- [Mike] Oh ho,
it's lots of fun.
(chuckling)
- Okay, they're kissing.
- [Tom] No.
- And they're dancing.
(humming along with music)
Back to the band.
Now kissing and dancing.
(mock sobbing)
(sucking)
(breathing heavily)
- Okay, fun time's over.
Let's get outta here.
- [Mike] Yep.
She's blond.
I was making out with
her, pretty much.
- [Woman] Stand at attention.
- Suck in that gut.
Pyle.
- You can get these
guys' phone numbers
when we have more time.
Right now we've got a job to do.
Spread out in singles.
Come on.
Let's move.
- [Tom] Is this anyway
to run an airline?
You bet it is.
(chuckles)
Please kill me.
(humming along to music)
- [Mike] Hey, baby, over--
(choking)
- Jane Goodall works her magic.
- A little bit
more with the hip.
No, no.
To the side.
- [Tom] Please kill me.
- How's this?
- Oh, Tiger, you're just
not getting the feel of it.
- [Mike] Oh, god, I was
gonna get through this movie
without thinking about
his hips, and now this.
- [Tom] Oh.
- Tiger, why don't you
let me out of here?
You can do it.
Please?
- Hey, I think
you're running down.
I think you need another pill.
- I don't want another pill.
I'm tired of being happy.
- [Tom] But it's a
good kind of tired.
Hmm.
- [Mike] Phew.
Well, you're out of paper.
I had to use Heathcliff.
He didn't mind.
(chuckles)
- I've just come
up from the cave,
and Rat Fink wants you to
finish your work down there.
Now Batwoman and her girls
are all over the beach.
And he said for us to
put operation plan Grab
X12 right away.
- Oh, stop pretending
there's a plot.
Don't cheapen yourself further.
- [Tom] Huh.
- [Mike] "Baywatch."
- Ooh.
- [Mike] Yes, "Baywatch."
- [Batwoman] Batwoman
monitoring 223.
- [Tom] Huh.
- [Batwoman] I'm passing
the reef south of the point.
Batwoman over.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
Batwoman monitoring 223.
- [Tom] Uh.
- [Batwoman] Come in 14.
- [Tom] Was that
part of the movie?
Or did that actually happen?
- Huh.
When Gidget meets Zorro.
- [Mike] See, now a
lot of villains aren't
bold enough to wear clamdiggers.
- Uh-uh.
- [Tom] Mom, do you ever
have a problem feeling fresh?
But mo, mom?
- She went on the
beach not expecting
to be abducted by
a Mexican wrestler.
- [Mike] Bad touch, El Santo.
- [Tom] Here's Charro
waiting to be abducted.
Ah coochie coochie
coochie coochie.
(choking)
Ahh!
- Well, that's five.
He's got a volleyball team.
- [Tom] Kind of looks
like a whiskey decanter.
A bottle of port.
Hm?
Hmm.
- You know, to me that leash
screams unhealthy relationship.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
- Careful.
You gotta watch your
footing down here.
I'd slow up for ya,
but we gotta catch up
with the rest of them.
Otherwise, they'll
think something's wrong.
- So?
- [Mike] I see your point.
- Well, it might mean
I'll lose my job.
- Big deal.
- [Tom] Taming of the Bat Shrew.
- Everybody's gotta have a job.
- Sure.
Everybody's gotta have a job.
So go ahead and do it.
I wouldn't ask you to
make any sacrifice.
- [Tom] One Adam
12, domestic one.
- Come on, little doll, be nice.
I know it's my fault I got
ya messed up in this place.
- [Mike] The first year
of bondage is the hardest.
- But you'd have
wound up here anyway.
And I gotta do what
they tell me to do.
- Sure.
- [Mike] Welcome to the mob.
- Come on.
We're just about
near the big cavern.
It's really something.
You ain't never seen
nothing like it.
- Ain't never seen
anything like it.
- Monsters outside
of Rat Fink's lab.
- I can't wait.
- It's just a tiny bit further.
Come on.
You're gonna see something.
- Tiger, what's that over there?
- Where?
(ominous orchestral music)
(screams)
- [Tom] Oh, that.
- Aw, they can't hurt ya.
They ain't even alive.
Come on.
- Eh, if they hit ya at 90 miles
an hour, they can hurt you.
- [Tom] Sounds like Bernie
Krause turning up his Melotron.
- Wow.
- [Mike] Fritz Lang's "Beaches."
- Didn't I tell ya?
This place is something else.
- [Tom] They got
great ribs here.
- This was a city
thousands of years ago.
Pretty weird, huh?
- [Mike] Yeah, too bad
it's not in the same movie.
- I'm scared.
- [Mike] Have sex with me.
- [Tom] Hm?
Woah.
- Looks like they're
stopping to rest.
Dr. Neon usually
movies real fast
when he's gonna
see his monsters.
- [Mike] What the,
hey, wait a minute.
(growling)
- [Tom] It's the mole people.
These movies have crashed.
(growling)
- Oh, I got a bad
worm or something.
Oh.
- [Mike] You got your mole
people in my Batwoman.
- [Tom] You got your
Batwoman in my mole people.
(growling)
- [Mike] Oh, well.
- [Tom] Well, I've had
enough of that film.
(groans)
- That's a slimming
look for him.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Mike] Dagnabbit, Pepino, get
the horses back in the barn.
Jesse.
♪ And I would walk 500 miles-- ♪
(laughing)
- You're going the wrong way.
- [Tom] Hm?
- My, my, my, my, my monsters.
- We are looking desperately
for a movie to be in.
(babbling)
- Go back to the lab.
- But I must see them first,
just a quick, teensy look.
He may be mistreating
them again.
Or he may be hurting them.
- Shh.
Don't worry.
- [Mike] The doctor dresses like
an off-duty Denny's manager.
- He's got more important
things on his mind.
Come on.
- [Tom] Come on.
Let's go.
(whistling)
Gotta go hurt Crow.
(singing)
- [Mike] But there's
mole people back there.
- [Tom] No, we gotta
go hurt you, Crow.
(doors clanking)
(whistling)
- Hey, Tom, what's up?
- Meeting of the
Satellite of Love crew.
- Hm?
- Oh, I don't think you'd
want to come to this meeting.
Is about you.
- Me?
- That's right.
It's about how you
cheated and betrayed
the confidence of a
sweet, innocent robot.
It's about how you made a
mockery of everything that's
good in this world.
It's about how everything
you touch you destroy.
- So why can't I come?
- D'oh!
Would you just--
- Oh.
- Sorry I'm late.
- Hi.
Well, as unpleasant
as this whole mess
is, we have to address
Crow's cheating.
I call this meeting to order.
- Guilty, guilty,
guilty, guilty!
- Tom.
- He's guilty.
- Come on, Tom.
Sure, Crow's made a mistake.
But we should have compassion.
Remember, my gumball-headed
young friend,
the quality of mercy
is not strained.
(sighs)
It falleth from the
heavens like a gentle rain.
- Gypsy, he stole
from your essay.
- Really?
Fry him!
I want to fight.
- There you go.
- I want to put him
under the ground.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- That's the spirit.
- Hey.
- Oh?
- Calm down, this isn't
getting us anywhere.
I think the first thing
that we need to do--
(singing)
- Hey, who's this guy?
- Ah, would you like some soup?
- Well, yes, I would.
That's exactly, oh,
would you knock that off?
- It's Crow.
- Get outta this meeting.
All right.
Now, uh, I think we
all agree that Crow
needs some sort of punishment.
What should it be?
- Well, if, uh, I may quote
from my colleague Gypsy
here, fry him!
Fry him!
Burn him up!
And if I may just interject
one thought of my
own, tear him up!
Rip him apart!
Burn him!
And in conclusion, die,
die, die, die, die, die!
Any thoughts?
- Yeah.
Well, actually I
was thinking more
along the lines of not giving
him any Hostess Sno Ball.
(whistling)
Hey, Crow, buddy.
- Yeah?
- I hate to be the
one to tell you this.
We all talked it over,
and we've decided to, uh--
- Shun you.
- Yeah, we'll I'm shunning you.
- Well, I shun you first.
- Yeah, I shun you back.
- I double shun you, version 2.1
- I shun you version 2.2
- I shun you version
three for Windows.
- This isn't
getting us anywhere.
We'll be right back.
- [Tom] I super mega
frigging shun you.
- [Crow] I frigging
shun me back.
- [Tom] Oh, yeah,
well, I giga shun you.
- [Crow] Yeah, well,
I shun you next.
- [Mike] No one's shunning.
Let's watch this, please.
- [Tom] Fashions by
Jean Paul Gaultier.
- - [Mike] Shut up.
- [Tom] Oh, he must be going
to a Packer game later.
(chuckles)
Oh, god, he's gonna drink
Liz Taylor's "Poison."
- Rat Fink is an
incredibly villain.
He isn't focused at all.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
Although he did have the
right amount of chains.
- [Mike] Mm, convenient.
- Who will be Miss
Chrysanthemum?
- This nectar, my dear girls,
is the most potent tranquilizing
agent ever devised.
- [Mike] Yeah, fine.
Just don't tickle us.
- It gives me strength, enables
me to solve great mysteries
that mortal man has
never dreamed of before.
(laughing)
- [Tom] Like how did Thea
the Doll get a series?
- I'd ask you to
join me, but then you
will have your opportunity
sooner than you realize.
(laughing)
- [Mike] Could you
hang us upside down?
We're Bat Women.
- The tranquilizer habit.
You ain't nothing if you can't
swim without them, fatso.
- Now you hear this.
I'll have none of
your insolence.
You're in no
position, any of you,
to show off your bad manners.
- Manners, he says?
(laughs)
- Oh, hang on.
Let me check my soup.
- All right, Neon.
I'll throw the dark current.
- [Tom] Now do it now.
(laughs)
I'm throwing the
dark current now.
♪ Jingleheimer Schmidt ♪
- [Mike] Hi, we're
back from Camp Snoopy.
(chuckles)
- Uh, are we in this scene?
Or are we supposed to be
back with the mole people?
(groans)
- [Rat Fink] Where's
the other girl?
Isn't she with you?
- Uh, Tiger is
locking up the place.
He'll bring her
right along to you.
(chuckling)
- [Rat Fink] Oh, good.
- [Tom] Uh, should I just
throw these on the bed, or--
- [Rat Fink] We have
room for just one more.
(laughing)
- [Mike] You're funny, Bat Fink.
- Well, Neon, what do you
think of our little menagerie?
(chuckling)
- It's marvelous,
simply marvelous.
What is it?
- I gotta go again.
- What?
- I gotta go.
- [Tom] Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Do do do.
- All right.
But don't cause any commotion.
Uh, walk slowly now.
- [Tom] You know, David
Bowie did the stage version.
- [Mike] Oh, yeah.
- [Tom] He had King
Vitamin for breakfast.
- Rat Fink, you have
a perfectly beautiful,
beautiful collection.
- [Tom] Blaaa.
(imitating farting)
- If I may say so, this time
you have outdone yourself.
- Yeah, whatever.
I've got things to do.
- Yes.
But what I want to ask you--
- [Tom] Where in
Europe am I from?
- Uh, what I want to
ask you, Rat Fink is--
- Yes, Neon?
- [Mike] Uh, what's the
fastest land animal?
- Several days now
and, and, and, I,
I just want to look in on them
to see if everything is nice.
Then, I I will come right back.
I promise you.
- Never mind the monsters, Neon.
- Here's the Sex Pistols.
- On them myself.
- But you never let
me see them anymore.
You're always putting me off.
- [Tom] Hm?
- They are my
monsters, Rat Fink.
I, I created them with these--
(moaning)
Two hands, with this mind--
- Are you saying, Neon,
that my own creations
are something less than yours?
- [Tom] And you, Tin
Man, step forward.
- Of course not, Rat Fink.
Uh, we both know the,
the value your great work
will bring to the world.
- [Tom] Oh, get your
nose out of my butt
and go see your
precious monsters.
- You'll be quite
pleased to know, Neon,
that all of your monsters
will soon be multiplied.
- Uh, Mr. Fink?
Uh, sir, could we
get a pop over here?
- Why do you think I
have these girls here?
- [Mike] I give up.
Why?
- Partners would be
difficult to find.
(laughing)
- Stop laughing like that.
- The offspring should
be most interesting.
(laughing)
- [Mike] Stop it.
(groans)
- Those girls and my monsters?
Oh, why that's,
that's wonderful.
- At what point do
they free Willy?
- [Mike] Hey, huh?
- [Man] Okay, Tiger,
I'll pull the switch.
- [Mike] You know, it's
possible they're making
an electric Santa Claus.
(chuckles)
- [Tom] At this point, they
could be doing anything.
(suspenseful orchestral music)
- You.
- [Tom] I like her.
- Yes, it's me.
(babbling)
You're wondering
how I found you.
(grunts)
- You should know
me better than that.
- [Tom] My breasts led me here.
- A cave, of all places.
It was so elementary, Rat Fink.
I don't know how you
could have taken the bait.
- [Tom] I'm still here, and I--
- I knew you would
kidnap my girls.
And that's what I counted on.
- Hm.
That's a homing device.
- [Tom] But men like it too.
- Each one of the girls
carries oscillators
set for my own frequency.
And this not only picks
them up but also frees them.
(laser gun beeping)
(chains crashing)
Free the others.
Use your magnetic
electron device.
- Well, why don't
I just unhook them?
- Hey, Tiger, why'd you
let her creep up on you?
- [Mike] I can hear
my heart breaking.
- I didn't have to
creep up on him.
He realized of his
own making that he
would do the honorable thing
and set that girl free.
- [Tom] Hmm?
- This boy has fallen in love.
(all chattering)
- [Tom] She's recapping
things from other movies.
- Uh, may I introduce myself?
- [All] No.
- My name is Flanagan,
Jim Flanagan.
I am vice president of the
Ayjax Development Corporation.
- We're all vice presidents
of the Ayjax
Development Corporation.
- Have a little pow-wow
that we can iron
this out and put it a new way.
Uh, um, Mr. Rat Fink, I
understand you have our, uh--
- [Mike] Hold the
microphone steady, Batwoman.
- Thank you.
That's a very good idea, to,
to sit down and talk things
over around the table.
I could whip up
something for the brain.
(babbling)
I will have something
for all of us,
and I have something
else for you in mind.
- Yes?
- Forget it, professor.
- [Tom] I'm holding
the hair dryer.
- Of those pills of yours.
I have no desire
to be made happy.
- Well, how would like to
try out the poison pill?
(babbling)
- Well, professor, now
that you mentioned it,
maybe just a little--
- [Rat Fink] Now listen to me.
I've had enough of this
dribble, all of you.
- Speak into the mic.
- You're forgetting
where you are.
- [Tom] And what
movie you're in.
- [Rat Fink] This is a
sanctuary of science.
- [Tom] Hm?
Sanctuary.
- Was a place of discovery.
You'll carry out the
work of evil no longer.
And I'll find a
satisfaction I've
waited for much too
long, your true identity.
- Woah, my nose.
- Remove his mask, 14.
- [Rat Fink] No!
- [Mike] I think it's
going to be Tony Roberts.
- [Tom] I don't know.
- I fear your weapon,
Batwoman, but I
have no wish to be destroyed.
- Want some cider?
- I have an emergency
call for the revelation
of the greatest
discovery of my career.
- [Mike] Oh, great.
- My fabulous body divider will
render things most difficult
for you, I'm certain.
- Stay where you are.
- [Mike] Huh.
- All right.
I will.
- [Mike] The compliant
villain, can do.
- [Tom] Maybe it's Ron Leibman.
- [Mike] Hmm.
Yeah.
(laughing)
- I needed your
reflection, Batwoman.
I'm still over there, and
at the same time I'm here.
And look, I'm there
and there too.
(laughing)
- Or maybe it's Madonna?
Or John Candy?
Or Adrienne Barbeau?
- Oh.
Hold them.
(laughing)
- [Rat Fink] You'll
never catch me.
(mocking laughter)
I'll keep on dividing
myself until you lose count.
(laughing)
- [Mike] I'll divide myself
into quarter acre lots.
I'll build houses so
close to myself, you
won't be able to catch me.
(mocking laughter)
(upbeat jazz music)
- [Tom] What is this?
Some kind of a weird-ass
hootenanny all of a sudden?
♪ It's a hootenanny ♪
- [Tom] Gina.
- You know a movie
is bad, bad, bad
if it makes "The
Monkees" look good.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
♪ I know that you are out
there somewhere having fun ♪
- [Mike] You never come
and see the baby, you rat.
- [Tom] This is like a classic
"Loopy de Loop" episode,
except I'm laughing
to kill myself.
(chuckles)
- [Mike] Maybe they'll all
turn into butter and nuts.
- Woah.
There's a bride
for every brother.
- [Tom] Okay, okay.
People, if I could get
all the dancing Rat Finks
to one side of the stage and
all the singing Rat Finks
to the other, please.
- And you never help
me around the house.
I hate you.
- [Mike] Zany, huh?
I wish I was hanging
by that rope.
- [Tom] Yeah, me too.
- [Mike] Looks so good.
(hiccupping)
- Uh, just one more.
(glugging)
- [Tom] Bless you, bless you.
Go in peace.
- [Mike] Excuse me.
That's my cape.
Excuse me.
- [Tom] Kill me.
Kill me.
(upbeat music)
(upbeat jazz music)
- Batwoman, can
you do something?
Somebody's gonna get killed.
- Definitely acceptable losses.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Mike] I think so.
- Allowable capacity
of 2.2 micro-serum.
If the cap--
- [Mike] Wait.
What?
- Electronic cease to floor--
- Take two a day until
the rash goes down.
- Start his equipment.
- Well, if he has
power enough, I'll
need several thousand volts
linked with what I have.
- I'm trying to get
all things considered.
- You can do it.
Now turn this
slowly, very slowly.
(singing along with music)
- [Mike] Thank you.
We wish we could hire you all,
but there is only one part.
You were all
wonderful Rat Finks.
- I can say one thing for you.
You have a tremendous
generating plant here.
- Thank you.
- It's been used properly
now for the first time.
Your little game has
finally come to an end.
- You'll not win out
over me, Batwoman.
(laughs)
- [Tom] I've got a pencil
sharpener and a bowl of sugar,
and I'll use them.
- You know what's
in this bottle?
It's Cobalt-40.
- [Mike] It's bubblicious.
- A few drops of this on the
hearing aid, and the atoms
will begin to split.
- Batwoman, he knows
about the mischief.
- I'll do it, Batwoman.
I'll do it if you force my hand.
(mimicking banjo music)
- I don't wanna
die because of you.
- You're a fink, Rat Fink.
(laughs)
(grunts)
- [Tom] Uh huh.
- Then that's it, Rat Fink.
Remove his mask.
(gasps)
- [Tom] William Faulkner!
- [Mike] Wow.
- Jb?
- Hideous.
- Please do not reveal
the secret to "The Wild,
"Wild World of Batwoman."
- But,
(groaning)
in all these years, you've
been leading a double life?
- You wild man.
- You went to all this trouble
to steal your own invention?
- I had to do it.
- Hello.
Hi.
Excuse me.
Ooh, excuse me.
Coming through here.
Pardon me.
- They insisted on 51
tickets being destroyed.
- [Mike] Oh, has
anybody seen my wallet?
- I couldn't allow that.
(humming)
- [Tom] Hm, nom, nom, nom.
- I just have one
little weakness.
- Weakness?
What weakness?
- Dove bars.
I love them.
- Well--
- [Mike] Somebody give
Heathcliff a rawhide chew.
- Little idiosyncrasies.
- [Tom] I stalk Rue McClanahan.
- My weakness is, I
know this sounds trite,
but I can't help myself.
- [Mike] I should be
sternly disciplined.
Oh, yes.
- I like to listen in on
telephone conversations.
The hearing aid was
designed for that purpose.
I realized that only by
having it stolen from
myself could I hope
to have it preserved.
- [Mike] Somehow
that got in there.
Sorry, folks.
- And neither will we.
- He spilled the Cobalt on it.
- [Tom] Huh?
- It's too late!
It's seeming through the outer--
(mimicking banjo music)
(humming)
- Oh.
(yelling)
- Neon, Batwoman, we gotta
find a way outta here!
- Be quiet.
- We must swim out to the ocean.
(mimicking banjo music)
- In a few minutes will
be the only way out.
Everyone, move!
- Well, I think we're
outta the woods as far
as chasing Rat Fink
around the table anymore.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
(humming)
(all screaming)
(upbeat rock music)
♪ People try to put us down ♪
♪ Talking about my gener-- ♪
(explosion booming)
- Woah.
- [Mike] Huh?
♪ I'll shoot myself if
we ever meet again ♪
♪ Doesn't matter where,
doesn't matter when ♪
This is my favorite
scene so far.
- [Tom] Mm.
- This one.
- [Tom] "The Wild,
Wild World of Batwoman"
now concludes its broadcast day.
(whistling)
- [Mike] In Grant Park,
on Lake Shore Drive.
(laughing)
(sobbing)
- Why?
Why?
- [Tom] They're
like drift babies.
Um, a little more
to the left, please.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- [Tom] Uh, pan left.
(chuckles)
- [Mike] Oh.
- Harder, harder.
This beach is just one
big litter box to him.
(groans)
- [Tom] Ew.
(grunts)
- Wars, Professor Neon.
(groaning)
Neon, what happened?
(grunts)
I can't remember a thing.
(laughs)
- Heathcliff, you've
gotten your voice back!
- Yes.
Yes, of course.
My voice, voice, I, yes.
- [Tom] And now it's
"Flowers for Algernon."
- I remember now.
It's coming back to me.
But, but it's been a long time.
- [Tom] Huh.
- Well, 14 years.
- [Mike] Another plot?
Oh, thank god, Heathcliff
got his voice back.
- We, we were working
on an experiment,
one that would bring
out the personality
traits of an animal.
- Yes.
- But Professor Neon--
- [Mike] What about
the hearing aid?
Am I crazy?
Wasn't that the plot?
- I gave you some
of the formula.
- You gave me some
of the formula?
- Mm-hmm.
- Me, your friend,
your benefactor,
the one who's
financing your work?
- Well, I--
- Mike, I demand
that you kill me.
- [Tom] Me too.
- [Mike] No, no.
- But I've taken care of you.
- [Mike] Can't have much to go.
- All of these years, I,
I've taken care of you.
And I'm thankful for that.
- [Mike] Will you kill me?
- But we'll have to
discuss this, Neon.
We'll have to discuss
this quite thoroughly.
Now come along.
Let's get away from this place.
- [Tom] And another thing,
you kissed me before.
What was that about?
- I, I can't straighten up.
(groans)
- [Mike] No.
- You can't
straighten your back?
(groans)
Well, don't fret, professor.
Just give me your hand.
- [Tom] Did we kill you?
- [Mike] Really, who could
not appreciate the irony here?
Huh?
(light orchestral music)
♪ And your brains
ain't up to par ♪
♪ And your ears
stick out too far ♪
- [Mike] Oh, Hamburger Hill
- [Bat Girls] We, the girls
who are dedicated to Batwoman
take out oath with
all sincerity.
- [Mike] Oh, boy.
- [Bat Girls] We, the girls,
who are dedicated to Batwoman,
take our pride
with all sincerity.
- And another troupe
is brainwashed.
- [All] We, the girls who
are dedicated to Batwoman,
fight against evil
with all sincerity.
- [Mike] Oh, no. Jackie
Vernon joined up with them.
- [Tom] He's not a girl.
- Now.
- You're one of us now, Tiger,
so you gotta do it right.
- [Tom] Uh-oh.
- [Mike] Oh, boy.
- Oh, no.
I have to think
about his hips again.
- [Tom] Avert your eyes.
Boy, their training is rigorous.
It's like the Israeli Army.
(upbeat rock music)
- [Mike] No, it's better.
- [Tom] Oh.
It's cuter.
Well.
- Heathcliff, what a
wonderful dual role.
- No, no.
Everything's quite satisfactory.
- [Mike] It's that
one Kid in the Hall.
- [Tom] Yeah.
He's turned into
Paul Lynde here.
(chuckles)
- Unheard of in my college days.
(singing along to music)
In fact, if I'd made
movements like that,
I'd have been firmly
boxed in the ears.
- Well, the music's
terrible, but at least
it's drowning out the dialogue.
- I figured out what went
wrong with Neon's experiments.
(babbling)
As a child, I fell on my head.
- [Mike] Good.
(chuckles)
- My turning into
a celestial genius.
- [Mike] Batwoman's medallion
is just like right there.
- The explosion,
of course, brought
upon the very same results.
- [Mike] Hmm?
- You know, it's simply amazing
what can be accomplished by--
- [Tom] Meh.
- A simple blow to the head.
(chuckles)
- Hi.
I'm Merv Griffin.
- Now hold still.
- Oh.
- [Tom] What a talent.
Shelley Berman, folks.
- [Mike] You know, this
is what happened when,
when the guy that thinks he's
a hoot gets into a movie.
- [Tom] Yep.
(whistling)
- You're rather cheeky.
- [Tom] Ohh.
Woah.
You outta have that looked at.
- [Mike] I'll look at it.
- [Tom] My goodness.
(sighs)
- Oh no!
(chuckles)
- [Mike] If I ever
get back to earth,
the first thing I do--
- [Tom] See your family?
- [Mike] Nope.
I'm gonna hunt
down Jerry Warren.
- [Tom] Good.
- Slow down.
You're going to
dislocate something.
(laughs)
- [Tom] Not since Dean
Jones in "The Love Bug," eh?
- Oh!
Oh!
- [Mike] Oh, he's
leaving an oil slick.
Help!
- [Tom] Huh.
- Oh, Donald.
Oh, Donald.
Oh.
- [Tom] End!
End!
- [Mike] What a
wild, wild world.
- Please stay away from sharp
instruments for three weeks
after viewing this film, and
do not operate heavy equipment.
Thank you.
(doors clanking)
- So why does Crow get a
chance to respond, Mike?
- Well, it's due process.
As the accused, he's owed
a chance to defend himself.
- Oh.
- Plus, it gives him hope.
And that should make killing
him an even richer experience.
- Oh.
- We're not gonna kill him.
And take the hood off.
- Oh.
- Well, I'm here for
my last-ditch hearing.
I've got a statement.
Hi, everyone.
(chuckles)
Well, where to start?
- Should we listen?
We're shunning him.
- No, we should listen.
- Oh, good.
It's hard to shun,
I keep forgetting.
- If it please the court--
- It pleases the court.
Quiet, everyone.
(clears throat)
- As I think back on my life,
I see basically a good robot.
A robust and exemplary
youth was followed
by an unusually religious
and public-spirited
young adulthood.
Then I began my life of service,
being crushed into an ingot,
being hung upside
down in chains.
- [Gypsy] You know,
it's really true.
- Yet all that matters not,
for trouble has found me.
I stand accused of cheating.
And here is where the
story becomes complex.
- Complex?
You copied my paper.
What's complex about--
- Shh.
- If my actions, if
my creative methods
for obtaining information have--
- He copied my whole paper.
- Shh.
- If those methods have been
perceived by some as less
than on the up and up, this
causes me so much pain.
- Can we just kill him now?
- Perhaps, in my purity, I
did not recognize temptation.
(scoffs)
- The tragedy is
almost too perfect.
But I accept the consequences.
I forgive Mike for forcing
me into this situation.
He did not realize the
trap he was setting.
- Wait a minute.
- I forgive Servo and Gypsy.
- He copied my frigging paper!
- Down he goes!
Down!
- And I forgive myself.
- Huh.
- Thank you.
(chuckles)
- I await your verdict.
- Well, Crow, uh, first off,
it seems like you never really
got to the apology.
- Oh, uh, right.
(clears throat)
In an otherwise
selfless and velvet life--
- Velvet?
- I have cheated.
And when you cheat, you
make an eat out of C and H.
I'm sorry.
- The court finds
the defendant guilty.
(sobbing)
- Oh!
- But he's basically
a decent guy.
So he and all his
friends are sentenced
to eating Hostess Sno
Balls all night long.
- Yay!
- Whoo hoo!
(laughing)
- I was with ya
out of line, buddy.
- Really?
- I hope you never fry.
- [Crow] Oh, thank you.
- Hey, guys, wanna
read a letter?
- Hey, yeah.
- We got a letter here from,
uh, a guy named Eric Bauman.
Hey, put it up on still store.
And here's what he says.
He says, I will soon
be starting law school.
And I would like
to represent you
in a suit against Dr.
Forrester and TV's Frank.
- Oh.
- I could have used a lawyer.
- I believe that you
have on your hands
a clear case of wrongful
marooning in space
and may be entitled
to a large cash award.
- Wow.
Cash.
- Eric, you're gonna do
the right thing, son.
You're gonna protect
the firm, right?
And by the way, we
got some pictures
of you and your girlfriend.
- Oh, no, no, no.
Give them the address.
- Okay.
Address for the Mystery Science
Theater Information Club,
Post Office Box 5325
Hopkins, Minnesota 55343.
Do it today.
- What do you think, sirs?
- Hmm?
- I admit, I ask you
to do this, Frank.
I mean, I wanted to take a risk.
- And you did.
You did.
You really look--
(screaming)
- Oh, really?
That good?
The way the sideburns
are that way?
Well, I, I like it.
I do like it.
I'm very happy with my decision.
(chuckles)
Now be a dear and push the
button, will you, Frank?
Frank?
Oh, never mind.
I'll get it.
Woah.
(upbeat synth music)
(laughing)
- [Narrator] This has
been a presentation
from Comedy Central.